{\clip(190,219,190,219)\t(0,600,\clip(100,217,280,220))\t(16600,17100,\clip(190,217,190,220))}m 0 0 m 180 1 l 0 1 l 0 0 l 180 0
{\clip(80,220,300,220)\t(0,600,\clip(80,197,300,240))\t(3700,4200,\clip(80,220,300,220))}翻\h译
KKKwn\h\h\h莉莉斯内普\h\h\h\h马丁马丁回音山
Gashdany\h\h\h汤包小螺螺\h\h\h\hVioletCheng_
{\clip(80,220,300,220)\t(0,600,\clip(80,197,300,240))\t(3700,4200,\clip(80,220,300,220))}校对\h&\h后期
老佛爷lfy\h\h\h\h你以为列
{\clip(80,220,300,220)\t(0,600,\clip(80,197,300,240))\t(3700,4200,\clip(80,220,300,220))}总监
Netflix1207
片头推广合作洽谈\h请联系普罗米修斯邮箱\hPLMXS2016@GmaiL.com
瞧瞧你们俩  最近怎么样啊
Oh, what up. Look at you two!
棒啊  你好啊
All right! Yeah! Yeah.
喝吧
Drink!
你输了
You lost!
好吧  干杯  姐妹们
Okay, cheers. Chicks.
凯特  到你了
Kate, it's your turn.
我该给她发短信吗
Should I text her?
利兹·墨菲可别再晒美食照片了
Liz Murphy needs to stop posting pics of her food.
我们懂了  利兹  你是素食主义者
We get it, Liz, you're vegan.
我也不清楚  我就是想试一试
I don't know. I was thinking of trying it.
我可做不到  我想吃什么就要去吃
Not me. I like to eat what I want when I want.
你不就是这样变胖的吗
Isn't that how you get fat?
摄入过多的卡路里才是让人变胖的原因
Too many calories is how you get
我每天不会摄入超过1200卡  从不  你看
fat, and I never go over 1,200. Ever. See?
我需要那个应用  它叫什么
I need that. What's that called?
瘦身倒计时  很棒  特别好用
"Countdown to Skinny." It's so good. It totally works.
我们还继续玩这个游戏吗
Are we not playing the game anymore?
是这个吗
Is it this one?
倒忌时
不是  好奇怪  那是什么应用
No. That's weird. What is that?
如果你可以知道自己确切的死亡时间
"If you could know exactly when you were
你会想知道吗
going to die, would you want to know?"
听着好吓人
That's creepy.
-简介就是这么说的  -好酷啊
- That's literally all it says. - Awesome!
好了  新游戏  咱们都下载这个应用
Okay, new game. Let's all download it,
然后看看谁的死亡时间最早
and whoever is gonna die first has to
最早的那个人要喝完桌上所有的酒
finish all the drinks on the table.
-算我一个  -我也是  我这就下载
- I'm in. - All right. I'm so down.
我不来  我不想掺和这事
I'm out. I'm not messing with that.
别这么婊里婊气的
Don't be such a little beyotch.
就是个应用而已
It's just an app.
好吧
Okay.
是这个吗
It's this app?
等一下
One second.
我已阅读用户协议并接受条款和条件
取消\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h确定
-都准备好了吗  -开始吧
- Everybody ready? - Let's do it.
我还有63年
I got 63 years.
还不错  我的是32年
Nice. Mine says 32.
22年  及时享乐吧
I got 22 years. YOLO!
你的结果是多少  考特
What's yours say, Court?
考特
Court?
它显示我只有3个小时可活了
Um, it says I only have three hours to live.
3小时
37分
11秒
你要死了哟
You're gonna die!
你输了  喝吧
You lost! Drink up.
-天啊  埃文  过来  -怎么了
- My god. Evan, get over here. - What?
我们下了一个可以测试死亡时间的应用
We downloaded an app that tells us when we're gonna die.
-然后  -看看你女友的结果
- And. - Look at your girlfriend's.
-你为什么要下它啊  -不知道  大家都下了
- Why would you download that? - I don't know. We all were.
你最好别害死我最好的朋友
You better not kill my best friend.
你们太可笑了
You guys are ridiculous.
喝吧  考特
Drink up, Court.
-你输了哟  -什么啊
- You lost. - What?
-你打赌输了  所以你得喝  -快喝  快点  考特
- You did lose a bet, so you gotta drink. - Chug! Come on, Court.
都是满满一杯的  你们在逗我吗
These are all full. Are you kidding me?
我帮你喝  宝贝
I got you, babe.
-谢谢  -应该的
- Thank you. - Yeah.
瞧瞧  骑士风度接班人
Look at that. Chivalry is not dead.
-放松一点  -好  我要走了
- Lighten up. - Yeah. I'll go.
这是凯特的
It was Kate's...
宝贝  你不能开车  你醉了
Babe, you can't drive. You're wasted.
你知道我醉的时候开得更好
You know I drive way better when I'm drunk.
这可不是开玩笑
That's not funny.
我开玩笑的
I'm kidding.
一起溜达回我家吧
Let's just walk to my house.
天啊
Oh, my God.
别跟我说你还在担心那个愚蠢的应用
Please don't tell me you're still worried about that stupid app.
宝宝  我发誓  我绝不会害死你的
Baby, I swear, I'm not gonna kill you.
我明白
I know.
走吧  就把车留在这吧
Come on. Let's leave the car here.
我不喜欢你这么做
I hate when you do this.
好吧  无所谓  我自己走回去算了
Okay. You know what? Fine. I'll walk by myself.
考特  考特  别闹了
Courtney. Courtney, come on.
考特  别闹了  我没事的  快上车
Courtney, come on! I'm fine! Get in the car!
别这样
Please don't do this.
跟你说过了我走回去
I told you I'm walking.
好吧  随你便
Fine. Whatever!
倒忌时
已违反用户协议
分
秒
蠢应用
Stupid thing.
分
秒
停下来
Stop!
关机\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
分
秒
{\move(189,200,189,240)\fs32\fad(1500,4000)\fscx100\fscy100\t(0,9000,\fscx200\fscy200)\fn等线}忌
{\move(120,200,100,230)\fs32\fad(1500,4000)\fscx100\fscy100\t(0,8000,\fscx200\fscy200)\fn等线}倒
{\move(255,200,275,230)\fs32\fad(1500,4000)\fscx100\fscy100\t(0,8000,\fscx200\fscy200)\fn等线}时
谢谢
Thank you.
-不错吧  -对啊
- Not bad. - Yeah.
奎茵  静脉注射交给你了  可以吗
Quinn, can you take over this IV?
当然可以
Oh, sure.
别担心  她是我们最好的实习医生之一
Don't worry. She's one of our best interns.
我告诉过你不能再来这里了
Hey. I told you you can't keep coming in here.
这里到处是石棉和铅  鬼知道还有什么
There's asbestos and lead, and God knows what.
再给我一分钟  拜托
Just one more minute, please?
好吧  就一分钟
Okay. Fine. Just one minute.
但你要知道  如果我死在这了
Just so you know, if something in
我做鬼也会缠着你的
here kills me, I am haunting you.
感到紧张很正常  手术确实挺吓人
It's normal to be nervous. Surgery can be scary.
但我保证  你会没事的
But you're gonna be fine, I promise.
不是这样的
It's not that.
你说得对  但是
I mean, it is that, but...
算了  你会把我当成精神病的
Forget it. You'll think I'm a psycho.
那你更得说说了
Ooh. Now you have to tell me.
你不能吊起我胃口又不告诉我
Can't just dangle the word "psycho" and not tell me.
小时
分
秒
我看不懂
I don't get it.
这个应用  会告诉你什么时候会死
It's an app that tells you when you're gonna die.
老兄  你不会信了吧
Dude, seriously?
我懂  我也说过这话
I know. I said the same thing.
但是它预测到了我们会出车祸
But it knew we were gonna crash.
等等  当时车里还有别人吗
Wait, there was someone else in the car with you?
不  她没上车
No, she didn't get in, um,
因为当时她的应用显示9分钟后她就会死
because that app said she was gonna die in nine minutes,
然后  9分钟后我就撞了
and nine minutes later I crashed my car
一根大树枝穿过了她的座位
and a tree branch went through her seat.
所以  你感觉她本来必死的
So, you feel like she would have died.
但她没有  对吧  这说明这应用是骗人的
But she didn't, right? What does that tell you about your app?
她确实死了
She did die.
就死在那天晚上
She died that same night.
应用知道的  它对她的预测是真的
It knew, all right? It was right about her.
现在它说我会死在手术台上  所以
And now it's saying that I'm gonna die during that surgery, so...
听我说  你这么聪明肯定知道
Listen to me. You're smart enough to know
这个应用就是一个啃老的废物做出来
that this app was made by some loser in his parents' basement
吓唬人的
trying to scare people.
走吧
Come on.
到时间了
Your minute's up.
埃文  我跟你说过那是禁区
Evan. I told you that's off-limits.
你不能总是去那
You can't keep going back there.
他知道
He knows.
他只是需要自己一个人静静
He just needed a minute to himself.
跟我来
Follow me.
坏事了
Shit.
恭喜
Surprise!
听说你通过了考试
We heard you passed your test.
你正式加入我们了
You're officially one of us.
-欢迎  欢迎  -好了  好了
- One of us. One of us. - Okay. Okay.
-怪胎  -你才是
- Freaks. - You're a freak.
天啊
Oh, my God.
-谢谢  -你自己争取的
- Thank you. - You earned it.
第三片了吗
Is that slice number three?
对
Yep.
你是想得糖尿病吗
So you want diabetes, then?
我爷爷一周能喝两箱可乐
My grandfather drank two cases of Coke a week,
还活到了94  所以  问题不大
and he lived to 94. So, I'm good.
知道吗  有个应用就是预测寿命的
You know, there's an app for that,
想确认的话可以看一下
in case you wanna know for sure.
这也是237号房的孩子告诉你的吗
Did the kid in 237 show you that, too?
为什么会有人想知道自己的死期
Why would anyone wanna know when they're gonna die?
我就想知道  应用叫什么
I wanna know. What's it called?
好像叫  倒忌时
Countdown, I think.
上帝可不想让我们知道这些
I don't think God intends us to know that.
上帝对咱们各有安排
God has a plan for all of us.
我们不该有疑问
It's not really our place to question when.
谢谢  这确实不合自然规律
Thank you. It's not natural.
该死  我只能活到87岁  夺命了  孩子
Shit! I'm only gonna make it to 87. Got robbed, kid.
我要把这应用发给你们
I'm gonna send it to you guys.
我可不想手机里有这玩意
I don't want that on my phone.
57年  意味着我能活到  98岁
Fifty-seven years. That'll make me... 98.
-瞎说  -是吗
- That's bullshit! - Is it?
我今早晨跑了6英里  你跑了多少
I ran six miles this morning. How many did you run?
0  但我依旧能活到87岁  所以  我赢了
Zero. But I'm still gonna make it to 87. So, I win.
救命  帮帮我
Help! I need help.
-慢点  慢点  -退后  闪开
- Hey, easy, easy. - Back up, back up.
-她吃了什么  -我不知道
- What did she take? - I don't know.
-她这样多久了  -不知道
- How long has shebeen like this? - I don't know.
拿两毫克的纳洛酮
Let's get two milligrams of Narcan.
奎茵  把阿片受体K给我
Quinn, grab me the OPRK.
拜托  醒一醒  拜托
Please. Come on, please.
-这是什么  -它能中和毒品
- What is that? - It's gonna counteract the drugs.
只要她不是中毒太久
As long as she's not too far gone.
振作  振作起来
Come on, baby. Come on.
如果你要打的话  赶紧打
Hey, if you're gonna do it, do it now.
好  打了
Okay. Here we go.
振作  振作  药来了  药来了
Come on. Come on. It's coming. It's coming.
好了  醒来了
There you go. There she is.
放松  放松  你没事了
Easy, easy, easy. There you go.
放松  醒过来就好  我们给你准备了蛋糕
Easy. Welcome back. We got cake for you.
放松  你会没事的
Easy. You're gonna be okay.
没事了  放松  放松
There you go. Easy, easy.
看看这个叫
"倒忌时"的新应用
下载
最终用户许可协议
输入您的信息
姓名  奎茵
生日\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
出生地\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
Harris
我已阅读用户协议并接受条款和条件
取消\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h确定
2\h\h天\h
22小时
37分钟
11\h\h秒
10\h\h秒
9\h\h秒
你不需要再戴学生证了  哈里斯护士
You won't be needing this student badge anymore, Nurse Harris.
谢谢
Thanks.
所以  今晚你打算去哪继续庆祝呢
So, where do you wanna continue the celebration tonight?
不能庆祝了
Oh. I can't.
我想要完成我的文书工作
I just really wanna finish my paperwork.
改日吧
But rain check.
我为你骄傲
I'm proud of you.
下次再约你吧
Gonna hold you to that rain check.
嘿  斯考特
Hey, Scott.
就很快问几个问题  我在填工作资格认证表
Quick question. I'm just trying to fill out my I-9.
提供的所有文件必须在有效期内
如果我没有护照该怎么办
What do I do if I don't have a passport?
用你的出生证明就好了  你那有  对吧
Just use your birth certificate. You have that, right?
没有  但我知道放在哪了  等会儿再打给你
No. But I think I know where it is. Hey, Can I call you back?
-好  没问题  -好的  拜
- Yeah, sure. - Okay. Bye.
该死
Shit.
上帝啊  乔丹
Jesus. Jordan!
-你吓死我了  -嘘  你会吵醒爸爸的
- You scared the crap out of me! - Shh. You're gonna wake Dad.
你到底在衣柜里干什么
What the hell are you doing in a closet?
这是乔
This is Joe.
你想穿件衣服吗  乔
You wanna put a shirt on, Joe?
非常想
Very much so.
我想我该走了
I think I should go.
我觉得这是个好主意
I think that's a good idea.
非常高兴见到
It was really nice meeting...
你不应该让男生到家里来
You shouldn't have boys coming over.
你不能告诉我该怎么做
You can't tell me what to do.
你又不是妈妈
You're not Mom.
如果我是的话
Well, if I was,
这种事你想都不会想
you wouldn't even think about pulling this shit.
你在这干嘛  奎茵
What are you even doing here, Quinn?
我要回家拿些工作上的东西
I had to come home to grab some stuff for work.
让我猜猜  既然东西已经拿到了
And let me guess. Now that you have it,
你就该走了吧
you're leaving?
很好  那再过六个月见
See you in another six months, then. Cool.
乔丹
Jordan.
-乔丹  -滚开
- Jordan. - Go away.
我今天有些好消息
I got some good news today.
我正式成为一名护士了
I'm officially a nurse.
-为你高兴  -奎茵小熊
- Good for you. - Quinny Bear?
一切都好吗
Is everything okay?
没事  抱歉  爸爸  我不是有意吵醒你的
It's fine. I'm sorry, Dad. I didn't mean to wake you.
过来
Hey, come here.
你饿了吗  需要我帮你热点什么吗
You hungry? You want me to heat you something up?
不用了  我正要出门
I'm okay. I'm actually headed out.
我要去上早班
I have a really early morning.
对了  如果你周六有时间的话
Hey. If you have any time on Saturday,
我们要去给你妈妈的墓地上放些鲜花
we're gonna go lay some fresh flowers up on your ma's grave.
好的  没问题  听起来不错
Okay. Sure. Sounds nice.
太棒了  好了  那我们周六来接你
Great. All right. We'll pick you up Saturday.
-好的  -好的
- Okay. - Okay.
-好了  -再见  爸爸
- All right. - Bye, Dad.
-我爱你  宝贝  -爱你
- I love you, sweetie. - Love you.
喂
Hello?
好了  还剩两分钟
Okay. Two-minute warning.
如果你需要上厕所的话快去吧
So, if you need to use the bathroom, use it now.
你会惊讶于多少人说了"不用了"
You'd be surprised how many people say, "I'm good,"
然后就有人来打扫过道了
and then it's cleanup on aisle five.
你需要帮助吗
You need any help?
不  我没事
No, I got it.
好吧  我马上回来
All right. I'll be right back.
别吓人
No freaking way.
喂  我在上班  一会回你电话
Hey. I'm at work. Can I call you back?
倒忌时用户破坏协议
好的  再见
Okay. Bye.
什么鬼
What the hell?
无法重新进入一楼
考特
Courtney?
Court?
嘿  发生什么了
Hey. What's going on?
那里发生了事故
There was an accident.
病人死在了楼梯井里
The patient died in a stairwell.
他们觉得可能是他自己跳下去了
They think he might have jumped.
哪个病人
Who was it?
237房的孩子
The kid from 237.
-埃文  -是的
- Evan? - Yeah.
你还好吗
You okay?
是的
Yeah.
他们收拾过他的房间了吗
Have they packed up his room yet?
嘿  瑞秋  艾米护士要见你
Hey, Rach. Nurse Amy needs to see you.
她刚刚让我收拾这间房
She just told me to do this room.
没事的  我来收拾吧
It's okay, I'll take care of it.
你应该去看看她有什么吩咐
You should go see what she wants.
好的  谢谢
All right. Thanks.
完成圆圈解锁
请将面部放在中央完成圆圈
无法识别
周六
和爸爸乔丹去拜访妈妈
家
喂  奎茵
Hey, Quinny.
喂  爸爸  你知道的  周六的那件事
Hey, Dad. So, um, you know, this thing on Saturday,
我跟医院确认了  那天我要上班
I checked with the hospital, and it turns out I do have to work.
没事的  工作很重要
That's okay. You know, work's important.
我们可以换个时间再去  对吧
We can go another weekend, right?
是的  事实上  这样正好
Yeah. In fact, this works out great.
你叔叔道格正要一起去北部工作
Your uncle, Doug, he's crewing up for a job upstate.
加班不错
It's good overtime.
等我回来我们再去
We'll do it when I come back.
好的  谢谢爸爸  爱你
Okay. Thanks, Dad. Love you.
我也爱你  奎茵
I love you too, Quinny.
-再见  -再见
- Bye. - Bye.
上班时间不能打私人电话
No personal calls when you're on the clock.
对不起  这种事情不会再发生了
I'm sorry. It won't happen again.
最好是这样
Better not.
倒忌时用户破坏协议
抱歉
Sorry.
我不是有意想要吓你的
I didn't mean to scare you.
汤普森女士的静脉点滴停了
Ms. Thompson's IV drip stopped.
-能来看一下吗  -好的
- Mind taking a look? - Of course.
这位可怜的女士已经昏迷了好几个星期了
This poor lady's been in a coma for weeks.
我知道  真遗憾
I know. It's sad.
我想只需要复位一下静脉泵
I think the IV pump just needs to be reset.
靠
Shit.
-你还好吗  孩子  -是的
- You all right there, kiddo? - Yeah.
事实上不好
Actually, no.
没事的
It's okay.
-没事的  跟我说说吧  -不
- It's okay. Talk to me. - No.
怎么了  发生了什么
What's the matter? What happened?
没什么  今天过得不是很顺
It's nothing. I'm just having a bad day.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
注册护士的第一天  我已经搞砸了
First day as an RN, and I'm already messing up.
看着我
Look at me.
你是位了不起的护士
You are an incredible nurse.
好吗
Okay?
你聪明又上进
You're smart. You're driven.
每次走进病人的房间  你都能让他们微笑
Every time you walk into a patient's room, you make them smile.
那是种天赋  好吗
That's a gift, okay?
过来
Come here.
开始的日子很难熬
First days are hard.
我该回去工作了
I should get back to work.
不好意思  抱歉  抱歉
Excuse me. Sorry. Sorry.
-奎茵  能问你个问题吗  -当然了
- Quinn? Can I ask you something? - Sure.
还记得你让我帮你执照
Remember the recommendation letter you
写的推荐信吗
asked me to write for your license?
-记得  -我滔滔不绝地写你
- Yeah. - I gushed about you.
我现在真的很想吻你
I really wanna kiss you right now.
我觉得这么做不合适
Oh, I don't think that's appropriate.
没事的
It's okay.
听着  没有人会知道
Look. Nobody has to know, okay?
这会是我们间的秘密
It could be our secret.
奎茵  你不是乐于助人吗
Quinn, you like to help people, right?
也许我们可以互相帮助
Maybe we could help each other.
我真的不舒服
I'm really not comfortable.
不  我说了不
No! I said no!
放开我
Get off of me!
住手
Stop it!
上帝啊  奎茵  你哪根筋搭错了
Jesus Christ, Quinn. What the hell is wrong with you?
得了吧  我看到你看我的样子了
I mean, come on. I see the way you look at me.
你是狐狸精吗
What are you, some kind of tease?
听着
Look...
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
我以为
I thought...
我刚才的做法很不专业  对不起
That was really unprofessional. I apologize.
好吗
Okay?
我们回去工作吧  好吗
Let's just get back to work, okay?
当然了
Sure.
你好  艾米护士
Hey, Nurse Amy?
怎么了 奎茵
Yes, Quinn.
我能和你谈谈吗
Can I talk to you for a sec?
艾米  更新一下克莱因太太的器官检查
Amy, I need an updated vitals check on Mrs. Klein.
-好的  我马上过去  -是很重要的事
-okay, I'll be right there in a second. - This is important.
艾米护士  请马上过去
Nurse Amy. Now, please.
奎茵  我们能以后再谈论这件事吗
Quinn, can we talk about this some other time?
倒忌时用户破坏协议
手机应用无法删除
如何解决这个问题
死亡倒忌时应用
17岁少女惨死于离奇事故
简明新闻-当局称一名少女在家准备洗澡时滑倒不幸身亡
17岁的考特死于家中浴室,据父亲所说,死因为滑倒导致的昏厥
家庭成员称考特摔倒撞到头部是正准备洗澡,但法医还未正式公布死因
"我们不知道"考特父亲说"我们不知道事情是怎么发生的"
后续报道将于法医公布更多细节后发布
真悲惨啊  她那么年轻又漂亮
我那天晚上和她在一起  她下载了一个准确预测到她死亡事件的应用  好诡异
这事也发生在我朋友身上了  现在她已经死了  一定要看
好了大家  这个倒忌时应用
Okay, you guys, this Countdown app thing,
我开始听到和看见一些东西了
I'm starting to hear things and see things.
比如昨天我看见了我的表弟
Like, last night, I saw my cousin
他四月就死了
who died in April.
我看见了他  他开始和我说话
I saw him, and he started talking to me.
我知道这是真的
I know it's real,
它在戏耍我  它在玩弄我
and it's toying with me and it's playing with me.
它在玩这个猫抓老鼠的游戏  我能感受到
And it's playing this game of cat and mouse, and I can feel it.
就好像它在吸食我的恐惧
And it's like it's feeding off of my fears.
我的时间快到了
My time is up.
这种感觉
And it feels...
天哪  天哪  天哪
Oh, God. Oh, God. Oh, God.
它来了  它来了
It's here! It's here!
救命啊  救命啊
Help! Help!
奥斯卡奖得主  这个视频百分之百是演的
这都有人信
放屁
奎茵  你在干什么
Quinn! What are you doing?
你被赶出来了吗
Did you get evicted or something?
-乔丹  -等等  等一下
- Jordan, - hang on. Wait a second.
真不敢相信你被蟑螂吓成这样
I can't believe you got that freaked out by a cockroach.
它在哪里  厨房里吗
Where is it? In the kitchen?
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
你把你的手机怎么了
What the hell did you do to your phone?
我
Oh. I, um...
掉地上了
I dropped it.
从飞机上掉的吗
From where, a plane?
你收到了一个叫做"倒忌时"的通知
You have a notification from something called "Countdown."
上面说你只剩一天了
It says you only have one day left.
一天以后呢
One day until what?
没有什么
Nothing.
好吧  你为什么表现得那么奇怪
Okay. Why are you acting so weird?
你为什么不在学校
Why aren't you in school?
爸爸出差了
Dad went on his work trip.
我被塔尔伯特太太当成保姆了
And since it's your fault
但既然那是你的错
I'm stuck being babysat by Mrs. Talbot,
我想我可以待在这里
I thought I could stay here.
乔丹  现在不是时候
Oh, Jordan, now is not a good time.
"如果你可以知道自己确切的死亡时间
"If you could know exactly when you're gonna die,
你会想知道吗"
would you wanna know?"
上帝啊
Oh, my God.
所以你最近表现得像个怪人
Is that why you've been acting like such a freak show?
因为一个应用程序告诉你
Because an app told you
你只下一天可活了
you only have one day to live?
不  这是假的  很明显
No. It's fake, obviously.
可是我想知道
Well, I wanna know.
别
Don't!
你有什么毛病
What is your problem?
我很抱歉你一直被塔尔伯特太太当保姆
I'm sorry you're stuck with Mrs. Talbot,
但你不可以待在这里
but you can't stay here.
求你了  我从来没有要求过什么
Come on. I never ask for anything.
我说了  现在不是时候
I told you, it's just not a good time.
上帝啊  自从妈妈死后
God. Ever since Mom died,
你这个姐姐当得真的很不称职
you've really sucked in the big sister department.
别这么做  不要试图
Don't do that. Don't try to make
让我感觉愧疚来得到你想要的
me feel bad to get what you want.
告诉你一下  不管你觉得
Just so you know, whatever you thought
我和乔那天晚上在干什么
Joe and I were doing the other night,
我们今晚一定会再做一次的
we're definitely gonna be doing it tonight.
倒忌时
你还有1天4小时55分钟
滑动以查看计时器
下一位
Next.
我的手机死机了
My phone just quit working.
这原因还真是令人费解
I can't imagine why.
你每次都是这么"优雅"地把它放下的吗
You always put it down with such grace?
你一般会用它做些什么
What do we use it for, primarily?
大部分都是在发短信和刷脸书
Mostly just texting and Facebook.
你口袋里的这部手机
You have more computing power in your pocket
拥有比航天局载人登月时还要多的计算力
than NASA did when they put a man on the moon,
可你却"大部分都是在发短信和刷脸书"
but you use it for "mostly texting and Facebook."
所以人类是生来就被注定的
This is why humanity's doomed.
我不想看到你这种态度
You know what?
以为自己是个科技男就在这儿拽了
I don't need your smug "tech guy" attitude.
你的经理在哪儿
Where's your manager?
-我去叫他  -对  去找他
- I'm gonna go get him. - Yeah, go get him.
稍等  行  等会儿
Just hang on. Alright. Hold on.
您好  我是这儿的经理
Hello. I'm the manager.
小姐  您需要什么帮助吗
Something I can help you with, miss?
你刚刚给自己丢了个顾客  傻蛋
You just lost yourself a customer, smart-ass.
是嘛  你觉得我还能找到下一个吗  还是
I did? Do you think I'll be able to find another one, or...
下一位
Next!
我要一部新手机
I need a new phone.
好的  你想要哪一款
Okay. What kind of specs are you looking for?
这些是刚进的
These actually just came in.
好  就那个吧
Yeah. Sure. That one.
好的
Okay.
如果你能先  等我把卡给刷了
If you could just... wait till I run the card...
好吧
All right.
没关系  我相信你
Never mind. I trust you.
你的眼神告诉我你是一个
Something in your eyes says you're
正常的  头脑清醒的人
a normal, completely sane person.
需要我帮你转一下电话卡吗
Need me to transfer a SIM card over?
不  我都要全新的
No! I want all new everything.
-新手机  新号码  新流量运营商  -好的
- New phone, new number, new service. - Okay.
这个不在价目表上
Now, off the books,
只要700块  我帮你解除出厂限制
for $100 cash, I could jailbreak it.
这样一来  你想下什么软件都可以
You can have every app you'll ever need.
不用了  它出厂什么样就给我什么样
No, I just want it however it comes.
好吧
Okay.
给你
Here you go.
怎么样  可以吗
That's good?
还需要别的什么帮助吗
Anything else I can help you with?
没有了
No.
好的
Okay.
下一位
Next.
倒忌时
更新完成
-这踏马是什么  -什么
- What the hell is this? - What?
这个软件
This app!
为什么它会出现在这上面
Why is it on there?
真奇怪  你刚刚买了它吗
That's weird. Did you buy it?
我哪有时间买啊  你刚刚才把它打开了
When could I have done that? You literally just turned it on.
好的  深呼吸
Okay. Deep breath.
那我们删掉它就好了  来
We'll just delete it. Here.
你删不掉它
It won't let you delete it!
算了  给我吧
Just give it to me.
行吧  我们在大众点评上哦  叫医生的无线网
All right. We're on Yelp. Doc's Wireless.
记得给好评  谢谢了
Please leave a review. Appreciate it.
她刚刚说的那个软件叫什么
Hey. What app was she talking about?
嘿  倒车看路啊
Hey! Watch where you're going!
-对不起  -傻逼女司机
- Sorry. - Stupid bitch.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
怎么又是你  你是白痴吗
You again? Are you an idiot?
看看你对我的雷克萨斯做的好事
Look what you did to my Lexus!
嘿  我跟你说话呢
Hey! I'm talking to you!
嘿  嘿
Hey! Hey!
放开她
Let her go.
你想干嘛
What are you gonna do about it?
我想干嘛
What am I gonna do about it?
你可以现在离开  这样谁都不会受伤
Well, you can leave and nobody gets hurt.
或者你也可以继续待在这儿
Or you can stick around
不一会儿你就会发现我这人有点疯狂
and find out that I'm all sorts of crazy.
并且  我说的那种疯狂啊
And I mean the type of crazy where
是那种我发现我快死了的那种疯狂
I just found out I'm gonna die,
说不定我会捎上一个白种男人跟我一起死
and maybe I feel like taking a white man with me.
所以  你选吧  我完全不会在意你的选择
So, the choice is yours. I really don't give a damn.
淡定  老兄  只是点儿小碰撞而已  天呐
Relax, man. It was just a fender bender. Jesus.
你没事吧
You okay?
你也看见那些不干净的东西了对吧
You're seeing stuff too, aren't you?
我也是
So am I.
我只想知道  为什么是我们
What I wanna know is, why us?
酒吧
因为我们下载了它
Because we downloaded it.
不  肯定不是这样
No, that's not it.
其他人下载了  但是他们就能活到100岁
Other people download it, and they find they're living to be 100.
它说我违反了用户协议
It told me I violated the user agreement.
对  它也对我说了同样的东西
Right. You know, it said the same thing to me.
你有看吗
Did you read it?
条款及细则吗  看了  一字不落
The terms and conditions? Every word.
真的吗
Really?
骗你的
No.
你们想不想买张去南极洲的船票
You wanna buy a ticket to Antarctica?
想也买不了
Well, you can't.
因为只有政府和光明会的人才能去南极洲
Because only the government and the Illuminati have access to Antarctica.
明白没  那群狗娘养的
See? The sons of bitches!
行  要是我们逃到别的地方去呢
Okay. What if we go somewhere else?
不  没关系了
No, it's okay.
反正我们也没办法倒回去读它了
There's nowhere to go back and read it.
我觉得  肯定有什么在等着被我们发现
I think that there's gotta be something there
告诉我们答案
that could tell us.
你们这群人该醒醒了
You people need to wake up.
因为如果我们去了
Because if we go there,
我们就会发现南极洲
we'll be able to see that Antarctica
是地球的边缘
is the edge of the flat earth.
大概没什么不可能吧  格尔
I guess anything's possible, Ger.
要是我们有办法
What if there's a way for us to
再看一遍用户协议呢
look at that user agreement again?
听我说
Track with me.
要是我们能让某个人下载它
What if we got someone to download it
让我们看看条款  再点拒绝就好了
just so we could see the terms, and we don't accept it?
不行  这么做不对
No! That is wrong.
相信我
Trust me.
嘿  大伙儿们  我想问你们个问题
Hey, question for you guys.
你们有人听说过这个新软件吗
Have any of you heard about this new app
它能告诉你还有多久死亡
that tells you when you're gonna die?
听起来像是胡扯
Sounds like bullshit.
或许他们就是想让你这么想呢
Or maybe that's just what they want you to think.
随便吧  它叫倒忌时
Anyway, it's called Countdown.
直觉告诉我这不太妙
I don't feel good about this.
它是假的  就像犹太人大屠杀那样  对吧
It's fake. Like the Holocaust, huh?
当我没说  你去吧
Never mind. Go ahead.
谢谢
Thank you.
"相机  录音机  位置信息"
"Camera. Microphone. Location."
没问题  没问题  都可以
Yeah, yeah, yeah. It's fine.
"用户协议  接受条款及细则"
"User agreement. Accept terms and conditions?"
等等等等  你疯了吗
Wait, wait, wait! Are you crazy?
你怎么能看都不看条款和细则
You should never accept the terms and
就点接受呢
conditions without reading them first.
好  "用户使用该软件时"
Okay. "User shall use the application."
倒忌时
版权  倒忌时命运系统
重要  请于使用该软件前人仔细阅读本条款
条款
用户使用该软件时应当严格遵守协议  只要您收取  打开  或使用了包含倒忌时软件的安装包  您就同意这个结束用户用户协议是合法的有效合同  且同意签下该协议  您愿意遵守科技产品法与本协议内提到的所以条款及细则  用户应该接受他或她命运的安排    任何想从倒忌时里窃取用户信息并尝试扭转用户命运的人  将统统视被为违反本协议
除非您有另一张不同的由倒忌时命运系统  您对本协议的许可协议和保修协议
巴拉巴拉巴拉
Yada, yada, yada.
"用户应该接受他或她命运的安排
"User shall accept the terms of his or her fate.
任何想从倒忌时里窃取用户信息
Any attempt to use information derived
并尝试扭转用户命运的人
from Countdown to alter the user's fate
将统统被视为违反本协议"
will result in a breach of this agreement."
接受我们命运的安排
Accept the terms of our fate.
等等
Hang on.
我本来明天是要坐火车去看我阿姨的
I was supposed to take a train tomorrow to go see my aunt,
但这个软件说我那时会死  所以我取消了
but the app said that's when I was going to die, so I canceled.
我也是  我取消了跟我父亲和妹妹的旅行
I canceled something, too, a trip with my sister and my dad.
可能这就是我该死去的时候吧
Maybe this is when I was supposed to actually die.
格尔  别同意条款
Gerry, don't agree to that.
相信我  你不会想知道的
Trust me. You don't wanna know.
所以  无论我们做什么
So, no matter what we do,
我们都会在几个小时内死亡
we're gonna be dead in a couple of hours.
不错  不错  瞧瞧
Well, well, well.
看来老格尔能活到91岁啊
Looks like old Ger Bear's gonna live to be 91.
解决了
Figures.
我们走吧
Let's go.
我爱这个软件
I love this app.
我们觉得  发生在我们身上的所有事情
Whatever's happening to us,
都是因为这个软件
we think it's because of this app.
从我网上搜到的关于鬼的资料来看
From what I've read online about hauntings,
它们有的是灵魂  也有的是
there are spirits and then there are...
恶魔
demons.
但我不确定  所以我想和一位内行人聊聊
But I don't know. That's why I wanted to talk to an expert.
对  我觉得是一些邪恶的东西
Yeah. I mean, it seems like demon stuff to me.
当我们在讨论恶魔的时候
Well, when we talk about demons,
其实我们都是在暗喻
we're usually speaking metaphorically.
等等
Wait a minute.
所以你觉得恶魔是假的
So you don't think demons are real?
很抱歉  我不相信
I'm sorry, but no.
是这样的  我不太会处理这类东西
Look, this stuff... It's not really what I do.
但我认识一个人  或许会更
But I know someone who might be a little better...
有资格
qualified.
嘿  奎茵  我能跟你说两句吗
Hey, Quinn. Can I talk to you for a second?
好  我也正想和你说一说昨天的事情
Right. I wanted to talk to you about yesterday.
给我两分钟
Give me two minutes.
行吧  好啊
Yeah. Great.
我的时间可"多"着呢
Because I have all the time in the world.
现在我在自言自语了
And now I'm talking to myself.
那个  这间有人了
Yeah, hey, this one's taken.
嘿  伙计  我说这间有人了  用另一
Yo, buddy, I said this one's taken. Use another...
嘿  小屁孩  去另一个隔间行不
Hey, kid, use another stall.
你没事吧
You okay in there?
嘿  伙计  你需要我帮忙吗
Hey, buddy, do you want me to get you some help?
马特
Matt.
它在哪儿  马特  它在哪儿
Where is it, Matt? Where is it?
嘿  你没事吧  老天呐  你没事  你好得很
Hey, you all right... Jesus. You're good. You're good.
好呗
Okay.
我也没在这儿干多久
I haven't worked here that long,
沙利文医生是基础
and that Dr. Sullivan is this integral...
奎茵  坐下吧
Quinn, have a seat.
好的
Okay.
这是来自人事部的戴夫·安德鲁斯
This is Dave Andrews from HR,
艾米莉  我们医院的管理员
Emily, our hospital administrator,
而沙利文医生  你已经认识了
and you know Dr. Sullivan.
沙利文医生告诉我们发生什么了
Dr. Sullivan told us what happened.
是吗
He did?
是的  奎茵
Yes, Quinn.
我觉得我有义务告诉他们真相
I felt obligated to come clean and tell them the truth.
不用为了这个毁掉谁的一生嘛  对吧
This doesn't have to destroy anyone's life, right?
只是个小误会而已  没别的了
It was a simple misunderstanding, that's all.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
谢谢
Thank you.
但是你在我的办公室里那样把我堵在墙角
But you cornering me in my office like that,
是很不好的  这件事必须被处理
that wasn't okay. It needs to be addressed.
我堵你
I cornered you?
听着  你没什么好尴尬的
Look, you don't need to be embarrassed.
我只是想在事情恶化之前
I'm just trying to stop something
就把它解决的  仅此而已
before it escalates, that's all.
如今到处都是"他说她说"  还是得小心点
Today's world of "he said, she said," you can't be too cautious.
我得保护我自己还有我的工作
I have to protect myself and my practice.
还有这家医院
And the hospital.
基于沙利文医生的报告
Well, based on Dr. Sullivan's report,
我已经建议了立刻停职
I've recommended an immediate suspension.
-什么  -真的有必要吗
- What? - Is that necessary?
我们不能就是商议一下  把她调走
Can't we just do counseling, or transfer her...
真不敢相信  是他硬要堵我
I don't believe this. He is the one who cornered me.
怎么  我连说话的权利都没有吗
What? I don't get a say in this?
奎茵  如果这是真的
Quinn, if this is true,
你为什么没有立刻来找我
why didn't you just come to me right away?
我来了  但是那混蛋妨碍我
I tried, but that asshole beat me to it!
我们在试着帮你  奎茵
We're trying to help you, Quinn.
别越抹越黑了
Don't make it worse by lying.
别碰我
Don't touch me!
她看着就是个很不稳定的年轻女孩
She seems like a very unstable young woman.
我们要走了
We're leaving.
马特  走了
Matt, come on.
你怎么了
What's up with you?
没什么
Nothing.
有人吗
Hello?
有人能出来服务一下吗
Can we get some service out here?
你能稍微尊敬点吗
Yo, will you show a little bit of respect?
老天  该死
Jesus. Shit!
你听见没
Shh! Do you hear that?
你好啊
Hello. Hi.
哈利路亚  我饿死了
Hallelujah! I'm starving.
你们把我的外卖送来了吗
You guys got my Grubhub?
不  我们
No. We..
不是  我们只想问你一个问题
No. We just have to ask you a question.
你相信恶魔吗
Do you believe in demons?
很信
Big time.
我知道这事很难相信
Look, I know how hard this is to believe.
不  不
No, no, no.
对  是很难以置信
I mean, yes. It's hard to believe,
但我希望是真的
but I want it to be true.
我当然不是希望你们  这个
I mean, I don't want you guys to... of course.
但恶魔还是可以的
But demons, whoo!
一开始也是因为这个
I mean, that's kind of what got me
我才会选择当神父
into the cloth in the first place.
你们知道吗  圣经27章里
Do you know, demons are mentioned
有19章都提到了恶魔
in 19 of the 27 books of the Bible?
加大拉的猪群  行邪术的西门  伪经
Yeah. The Gadarene Swine, the Simon Magus, the apocrypha.
前二者分别出自《马太福音》《使徒行传》  第三者为没有列入正典《圣经》的经籍
抱歉  我没想跟你们显摆  只不过
I'm sorry. I don't mean to be geeking out on you. Just ahh!
我太爱这个了
I love this stuff.
圣经就像是最好的漫画小说
I mean, the Bible is like the ultimate graphic novel.
整件事都让我想起这个老故事
You know, this whole thing reminds me of this old story from...
阿门
Amen
找到了
Yes!
从前有一位年轻的王子
So, there was this young prince
他的父亲是众人爱戴的国王
whose father, a much-beloved king,
他已经很老了  差不多要咽气了
was old, like brink-of-death old.
国王身体已经不行了
With the King in such bad shape,
就要靠王子领兵打仗
it was up to the prince to lead the army into battle.
他就找到这个老的吉普赛女人
So he tracks down this old gypsy woman.
问她能不能告诉他  自己会不会活下来
And he asks her if she can tell him, will he survive the battle?
吉普赛女人给了他一个有数字的卷轴
The gypsy woman hands him a scroll with a number on it.
那个数字就是他死亡的准确时间
And that number is the exact moment of his death.
但她警告他
But she warns him,
"别用这个来救你自己
"Don't use this to save yourself,
别想改变你的命运"
to change your fate."
于是王子答应了  打开了卷轴
Now, the prince agrees, opens up the scroll.
不是什么好消息  一点都不好
News ain't good, not even a little bit.
知道他干了什么吗  过来
So you know what he does? Come here.
他派他的弟弟上战场
He sends his little brother instead.
但他的弟弟没有死
But his brother doesn't die.
事实上  他领导军队赢得了胜利
In fact, he goes on to lead the army to victory.
同时  懦弱的王子又去找了吉普赛女人
Meanwhile, our coward prince goes back to the old gypsy woman,
他向她发誓  "死亡天使要来接我了"
and he swears to her, "The angel of death is coming for me."
但是她保证  死亡天使不会来的
But she assures him Death is not coming for him.
来找他的一点都不自然
What's coming for him now, there's nothing natural about it.
是恶魔  奥辛
It's the demon, Ozhin.
王子改变他命运的那一刻  奥辛就来了
The moment the prince changed his fate, Ozhin came for him.
但不是为了杀他  是为了折磨他
But not to kill him, to torment him
一直到吉普赛女人预言他要死的那个时间
right up until the exact moment the gypsy predicted he would die.
谢谢  神父
Oh. Thanks, Father.
我感觉不能再糟了
I didn't think I could feel any worse.
我觉得  我也不确定
Look, I think... I mean, I'm not sure,
但这个应用看着就像是
but this app seems like a modern
那吉普赛女人预言的现代版
version of what the old gypsy lady did.
要是我能看到代码  应该就能确定了
If I could just see the code, I think I would know for sure.
你是说黑了应用吗
You mean like hack the app?
你们知道怎么黑吗
Do you know how to do that,
还是你们认识谁会黑的
or do you guys know someone who could?
我可能认识一个
I think I might.
我的外卖到底送哪去了
Where the heck's my Grubhub?
医生的无线网
-等下  等下  -关门了
- Hey, wait! Wait! - We are closed.
我们早些见过的  你说你能破解我的手机
We met earlier, and you said that you could jailbreak my phone.
是不是说明你会黑进一个应用
Does that mean you know how to hack into an app?
-对  -太好了
- Yeah. - Great.
我们需要你帮忙  十万火急
Look, we need your help. It's kind of an emergency.
抱歉
Sorry.
我的探探约会已经迟到了
I'm already running late to my Tinder date,
我也有段时间没约过谁了  所以抱歉了
and I haven't matched with anybody in a while. So, no.
等下  等下  你真想给那姑娘留个印象吗
Wait, wait, wait. You really wanna impress this girl?
这张信用卡的额度有两千美金
This credit card has a $2,000 limit.
对  这张大概还剩下三百美金
Yeah. And this one has about 300 left.
如果你帮我们  两张卡归你了
If you help us, these are yours.
求你了
Please.
感觉好违法
This feels illegal.
我喜欢
I like it.
抱歉  大概要十五分钟  可以吗
Sorry. It's just gonna be, I don't know, 15 minutes, okay?
我喜欢你的照片
I love your profile pic and I cannot
真的等不及见真人了
wait to see the real thing in person.
好的  一会儿见
Okay. Bye-bye.
好了  你们有十五分钟  手机呢
All right. You got 15 minutes. Phone?
就这个应用  这个
It's this app, right here.
真的假的  倒忌时
Seriously? The Countdown app,
就是告诉你什么时候会死
where it tells you when you're gonna die?
-蠢死了  -你下了吗
- That's so dumb. - Did you download it?
当然了  你那么疯疯癫癫让我很好奇
Of course. Your hysteria piqued my interest.
想法不错  就是形式很可怕
It's a great idea. It's just horrible execution.
不就是随机定个数字加倒计时
I mean, just a random number with a countdown?
也不是很吓人
It's not very scary.
不过你们俩傻子好像吓得不轻
Though, it seems like it worked on you two clowns.
麻烦  你搞你的
Please, please. Just continue.
好  谢谢
Okay. Thanks.
奇怪了  六十个G
That's weird. Sixty gigs?
倒忌时
-什么意思  -就是说它很大
- What does that mean? - That means it's big.
就像你手机上下了一整季《权游》那么大
Like "a season of Game of Thrones on your phone" big.
这说不通  它就是个钟
Which doesn't make any sense because it's just a clock.
-你还能删掉它吗  -当然了
- Can you still delete it? - Of course.
这是医生的无线网  我是电子产品的医生
This is Doc's. I'm the doc of technology.
我什么都可以
I can do anything.
你们看
Ha! Check it out.
我们黑进来了
Now we're in.
那是什么  "这会诅咒"
What is that? "Hoc maledictum te..."
-那是拉丁语  -你确定
- That's Latin. - Are you sure?
我去天主教高中上了四年  我确定
I went to Catholic high school for four years. I'm sure.
-很好  怎么说的  -不知道
- Great. What's it say? - No idea.
我人是在那里  心嘛
Physically, I was there, but mentally...
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
姓  名  这些是他们的倒忌时
Last name, first name. And look, these are their countdowns.
这么多人
There are so many.
看  那个是我
Hey, that's me.
32年零11天
Thirty-two years, 11 days.
德雷克·金  32年11天23小时41分52秒
等等  你们觉得
Hold on. How long do you guys think
漫威宇宙能活多久
the Marvel Universe will last?
四十年  五十年
Forty years, 50?
保险起见定个六十年好了
Let's just say 60, to be sure.
好了
There it is.
天啊  有效了  看他的手机
Holy shit. It's working. Look at his phone.
起作用了
It worked.
好了
Okay.
你叫什么  小姑娘
What's your name, pumpkin?
奎茵 哈里斯
Quinn Harris.
等等
Stop.
那是我妹妹
That's my sister.
乔丹 哈里斯  13小时29分43秒
该死  她果然也下了
Shit. Of course she downloaded it.
-她的时间和我的一样  -其实并不
- Her clock is the same as mine. - Actually, no.
她的还要短三分钟  看见没
Hers is three minutes shorter. See?
等等  她明天会和你在一起吗
Wait a minute. Was she supposed to be with you tomorrow?
对  该死
Yes. Shit!
先改她的
Change hers first.
你还有信用卡吗
Got another credit card?
好啦  不用不用  我会改的  我是好人
Okay. No, no, no. I'll do it. I'm a good guy. I'll do it.
倒忌时
你的倒忌时已更新  滑动查看
你知道规矩的  桌上不看手机
You know the rules. No phones at the table.
-但我  -明早你再来拿
- But I was... - You can have it back in the morning.
我才看了一眼
I was just looking.
谢谢
Thank you.
你真是天才
You're a genius!
真不是吹的
Yeah, no shit.
你还好吗
Are you still good?
很好
Yep.
我还有71年
I got 71 years left.
我还有点愧疚  可以活得比你久
You know, I kind of feel bad that I'm gonna outlive you.
别  95岁也太老了
Don't. 95 is way too old.
86岁我就很满意了
I'm happy with my 86.
那  要我
So, should I...
把你送到你车那边吗
drop you at your car?
好啊  当然好了
Yeah, yeah, sure.
不过我的车就在那边
Except for the fact that my car is right over there.
那我再打给你
I suppose I'll call you.
好  很好
Nice, real nice.
你今晚想一个人吗
Do you wanna be alone tonight?
一点也不
Not at all.
-你介意我开着灯吗  -一点也不
- Do you mind if I keep these lights on? - Not at all.
我一直在想约翰神父说的
I've been thinking a lot about what Father John said
是什么迫使我们想知道死期
about what compelled us to wanna know when we're gonna die.
我也是
Me too.
然后呢
And?
我十岁的时候
When I was 10,
我的弟弟杰夫生了场重病
my little brother, Jeff, got really sick.
我们基本上就住在医院
And we practically lived at the hospital.
那两年  我爸妈全部精力都在杰夫身上
My mom and dad could only focus on Jeff for those two years,
我能理解
and I get it.
但同时  我还是
But at the same time, I was...
很嫉妒他所到到的呵护
jealous of all the attention that he was getting.
他有一个玩具  我也很想要
He had this toy that I really wanted.
一个小恐龙机器人
This stupid robot dinosaur.
所以当他熟睡时  我把它拿走了
So when he was asleep, I took it.
我偷了我垂死的弟弟的玩具
I stole my dying brother's toy.
杰夫一直都很敬重我的
Jeff, he looked up to me.
而我现在反倒能活到95岁
And I'm the one that gets to live to be 95.
你那时只是个孩子
Yeah, but you were just a kid.
说说你
What about you?
是因为我妈妈
My mom.
她一直是家里的粘合剂
She was the glue in our family.
但她也很严厉
But she was tough.
后来
And...
有一天  我在家关禁闭
on one of the many nights I was grounded,
当时我最好的朋友正在开派对
my best friend was having this huge party.
我受够了我妈的管教
And I was so sick of my mom's shit,
就偷摸跑了
so I went.
我妈妈
My mom,
去找我回家时
she went out looking for me,
冲出来一个酒驾的司机
and one drunk driver later,
撞死了她
she was dead.
奎茵  这不怨你
Quinn, that's not your fault.
谢谢你
Yeah. Thanks.
你不用非得睡在地上
You know, you don't have to sleep on the floor.
好吧  不过
All right. But...
我得说明下
just so we're clear,
我不是那种随随便便和
I don't usually jump into bed with
通过应用认识的女孩上床的人
girls that I just met off of an app.
严格地讲  咱们是因应用而认识
Well, technically, we met because of an app.
有理
Good point.
马特
Matt.
醒醒  马特
Matt, wake up.
马特
Matt!
你叫我吗
Yo, are you calling my name?
奎茵  奎茵  奎茵  放松  放松
Quinn. Quinn. Quinn. Relax. Relax.
奎茵  醒醒  醒醒
Quinn. Hey. Hey. Hey.
你做了个噩梦
It was just a nightmare.
不不不不  时间又退回到了之前的样子
No, no, no. It went back to what it was!
0年
0天
4小时
32分钟
36秒
0年
0天
4小时
32分钟
35秒
见鬼
Oh, shit.
我的也是
So did mine.
不
Oh, no.
乔丹
Jordan.
来电提示
奎茵
6个未接来电
倒忌时
您的倒忌时已完成更新
滑动查看
0年
0天
4小时
16分钟
14秒
0年
0天
4小时
16分钟
13秒
塔尔伯特夫人
Mrs. Talbot?
乔丹
Jordan.
妈妈
Mom?
她在哪儿
Where is she?
你姐姐去哪儿了
Where's your sister?
她在哪儿
Where is she?
没事没事  是我
It's okay! It's me!
家里有鬼
There's something in the house.
我知道  咱们离开这儿
I know. Let's get out of here.
有人吗
Hello?
快开门
Open up!
约翰神父
Father John!
你们还好吗
You guys okay?
你们拿到代码了吗
Did you get the code?
又来个小姑娘
New girl.
我先把衣服穿上
I'm gonna shirt on.
进去吧
Come on.
这诅咒会一直伴随着你
"This curse will come upon you,
追赶着你  压制着你
will pursue you, and overwhelm you
直到把你彻底毁灭
until you are utterly destroyed."
太棒了  这真是妙啊
This is good. This is really good.
这哪里妙了
How is that good?
现在我们知道  咱们的对手是啥了
Because now we know what we're dealing with.
这是个诅咒
This is a curse.
诅咒来自于魔鬼和他的爪牙们
Curses come from the devil and his servants.
好消息是  诅咒是可破的
Good news: curses can be broken.
来  击个掌吧
Can I get a hallelujah high five?
好吧
Fine.
你们听着  撒旦是谎言之父
Look, gang. Satan is the father of lies.
如果能证明他说谎  诅咒即可破解
If you can prove him a liar, you can break the curse.
"证明他说谎"  这是什么意思
What does that mean, "prove him a liar"?
如果能与时间抗衡  证明倒计时是错的
If you can foil the clock, prove it wrong,
那么所有被诅咒操控的人就都能得救
it should lift the curse from anyone suffering from it.
你是说  必须有人在预定时间之前死掉
So someone has to die before they're supposed to?
这是方法之一
That would get the job done.
但没有人想马上死掉  对吧
But I don't think anybody here wants to die, right?
所以  我的想法正好相反
So, I'm thinking the opposite.
我们需要确保有人
We need to keep one of you alive
在倒计时结束后还活着
longer than you're supposed to be.
怎么能做到
How are we supposed to do that?
难道是死亡到来时
I mean this thing shows up
我们对他说  "等等  再等一会儿"
and we're just supposed to be like, "Hang on, I need a sec"?
就是这样
That's exactly what we're gonna do.
有这么一个护法阵图
See, there's protection rituals,
祷告可以多为你赢得一些时间
prayers that should buy you some time.
只要我们打破时间界限  哪怕只有一秒
All we need to do is beat the clock by one second.
你以前做过类似的法事吗
Have you ever done anything like this before?
没有  但我读到过  很多次
No. But I've read about it, a lot!
在这儿  在这儿
Here! Here! Here!
我找到了  找到了
Got it. Got it. Got it. Got it.
大家看
Look.
我们需要用盐铺出这个形状
We need to make this out of salt, right?
我祝祷过后   你们在阵图里就会很安全
Now, once I bless it, you should be safe inside.
不洁的灵魂无法穿越此圆圈
See, no impure spirits are allowed to cross this circle.
它应该  能够帮你们争取到时间
It should... buy you the time you need.
很好  那么  只有一个问题
Great. Well, I just have one question.
我们去哪儿搞到这么多盐
Where are we gonna get that much salt?
当然是我从超市买来的存货咯
I get mine at Costco.
-都跟我走  时间不等人啊各位  -快走
- Follow me! Come on! Clock's ticking, everybody! -Come on.
就这里  我先把灯打开
Right here. Let me just turn the lights on.
没错  快过来
Good. Right. Come on.
这是岩盐
Now, this is rock salt.
我除杂草用的
I use it to kill weeds.
这能管用吗
Will that work?
岩盐也是盐  只要祝祷过  大概能有用吧
Salt is salt. Once I bless it, we're good... I think.
-啥  -没事的  我们会安全的
- What? - No, we're fine. We're gonna be fine.
如果盐被吹散了  怎么办
What if it just blows the salt away?
这倒很有可能  我之前没想到
That could absolutely happen. I didn't think of that.
该死的  抱歉啊上帝
Goddammit! Sorry.
那我就祈祷它不被吹散
And I will pray it doesn't.
我想到个办法
I have an idea.
等等  给你这个
Wait. Here.
-拿着它  -你不觉得有点小吗
- Hold this. - Little small, don't you think?
架不在大  有神则灵
It's not the size of the cross, it's the power of the Spirit.
如果我们把盐混在这里面呢
What if we mix it with this?
你真是个天才
That is a genius idea.
好了  咱们先清理出一块空地
Yes. Okay. Let's clear out a space right here.
快  时间不等人
Great. Come on. Clock's ticking, guys!
我要画一个大圈  10甚至15英尺的
I'm gonna make a big circle. Ten, 15 feet.
加油  能搞定吗  很好
Come on. You good? Great. Okay.
好了同志们  开始
All right, gang. Here we go.
涂厚些  再厚些
Thicker, thicker.
主啊
Lord,
请赐予这些盐以力量吧
bless this salt.
让祢的光芒击退那些
Let Your light hold back the demons
企图侵入你的圣地的恶魔吧
that try to enter our world, Lord.
好了  再把阵图完善些  再完善些
That's it. Make that symbol perfect. Make that symbol perfect.
涂得越厚越好  越厚越好
Make that as thick as you can. As thick as you can.
那边再补一下
Now I want it right there.
完美  虽说画得不太圆
Pretty great! I mean, it's more of an oval than a circle,
但毕竟时间紧  任务重
but we're under a lot of pressure.
好了  马特的倒计时还有多久
Okay, how much time till Matt dies?
0年
0天
0小时
2分钟
32秒
0年
0天
0小时
2分钟
31秒
0年
0天
0小时
2分钟
30秒
0年
0天
0小时
2分钟
29秒
好了  阵图已经画得很好了  很好了
Okay, that symbol's good. That symbol's good. Okay, that's right.
很好  完成了
Correct. I got this.
-如果阵图不管用  怎么办  -会有用的
- What if this doesn't work? - It's going to.
万一没有用呢
No, but what if it doesn't?
听我说
Listen to me.
那就是盐和油漆
It's just salt and paint...
很好
That's good.
-我们该进圈了  -快来
- I think we should get in the circle. - Come on!
-奎茵  我好害怕  -我也是
- Quinn, I'm scared. - Me too.
好了  马上就要来了
Okay. This might actually be happening right now.
-我要去拿一个大点的十字架  -你说啥
- I'm gonna go with the bigger cross. - What?
-它在这里  -待在我身旁
- It's in here! - Stay close to me.
主啊  用祢的力量使我们强大起来
Strengthen us in Your power and might, O Lord.
用祢的盔甲将我们武装起来
Dress us in Your armor, Lord,
这样我们才能顽强地抗争恶魔的鬼蜮伎俩
so that we may stand firm against the machinations of the devil.
等等  它就在我们上方游荡
Wait, wait. It's moving above us.
-你看到什么了吗  -没有  你呢
- Do you see anything? - No. You?
也没有
No.
好
Okay.
等等  站到我身后
Wait, wait! Stay behind me!
阵图奏效了  他进不来
It's working! He can't get in!
滚回你的地狱去吧
Go back to hell.
-他去哪儿了  -他去哪儿了
- Where did he go? - Where did he go?
他去哪儿了
Where did he go?
-把手机关掉  -我在关  我在关
- Turn it off! - I'm trying! I'm trying!
-马特  关掉手机  -我在关
- Matt, turn it off! - I'm trying!
在那儿
There!
把它关掉
Shut it off!
马特  它在哪儿
Where is it, Matt?
杰夫
Jeffy?
你为什么拿走我的小恐龙
Why'd you take my dinosaur?
我本来要还你的  杰夫  我发誓
Jeffy, I was gonna give it back. I swear.
你没有
No, you weren't.
我没有
You're right.
杰夫  我很抱歉
Jeffy, I'm sorry.
马特  你看到什么了
Matt! What do you see?
杰夫  别走
Jeffy, don't go.
马特
Matt!
奎茵
Quinn!
乔丹  不要  不要出圈
No, Jordan, don't break the circle!
马特
Matt!
我们做到了
We did it.
他放了我
He let me go...
救命啊  救命
Help! Help!
0年
0天
0小时
0分钟
3秒
0年
0天
0小时
0分钟
2秒
0年
0天
0小时
0分钟
2秒
0年
0天
0小时
0分钟
1秒
0年
0天
0小时
0分钟
0秒
一会儿我就去找你了
I'll see you soon.
奎茵
Quinn?
他死了
He's gone.
-我太抱歉了  -我也是
- I'm so sorry. - Yeah.
不  这说得通  他的时间到了
No, it makes sense. It was his time.
我们的时间很快也到了
Pretty soon it'll be our time, too.
别这么说
Please don't say that.
我也不想  但你们刚刚都看见了
I don't want to, but you just saw what happened.
天哪
Oh, my God.
你在流血吗
Are you bleeding?
你在流血
You're bleeding!
我们需要帮助
We need some help in here!
-我们需要轮椅  -奎茵  怎么回事
- We need a wheelchair! - Quinn, what happened?
出车祸了  她的腹部被刺伤了
There was an accident. She has a puncture to the abdomen.
我们来  我们把她送进去  去找罗茜登记
Okay we got her. We'll get her right in. Go check in with Rosie.
好
Okay.
不  求你了  奎茵  别离开我
No. Please, Quinn, don't leave me.
我哪都不去  我就在这
I'm not going anywhere. I will be right there.
-别离开我  求你了  -我就在这
- Please don't leave me. Please. - I'll be right there.
很抱歉  亲爱的  你还好吗
Sorry, honey, are you okay?
直播  夜间新闻
突发新闻
是马特的火车
Matt's train.
还不算太糟  你很坚强  对吗
That's not too bad. You're pretty tough though, right?
奎茵
Quinn.
我能跟你谈谈吗
Can I talk to you?
-我真的  -我听说沙利文医生的事了
- I really... - I heard what happened with Dr. Sullivan.
我知道发生了什么
I know what happened.
我是说
I mean...
我自己知道
I personally know...
我只是想告诉你
I just want you to know
如果你的目标是他  我支持你
that if you go after him, I'm with you.
你会没事的  看着我
I think you're gonna be A-okay. Look at me.
谢谢你
Thank you.
真心谢谢你  瑞秋
Truly, thank you, Rachel.
好了
All right.
像你姐姐一样
Just like your big sister.
你们俩先聊
I'll let you two at it.
你会被照顾得很好的  孩子
You'll be in good hands, kiddo.
谢谢你
Thank you.
当然
Of course.
你没事吧
Are you okay?
疼吗
Does it hurt?
奎茵  我知道你觉得是你的错
Quinn, I know you think it was your fault,
妈妈的死
Mom dying.
是我的错
It was my fault.
什么
What?
妈妈问过我你去哪了  我是知道的
Mom asked me where you were, and I knew.
如果我当时告诉她了
And if I had just told her,
她就不会开车路过商场了
she wouldn't have been driving way over by the mall.
乔丹
Jordan,
某个闯红灯的醉鬼不是你的错
it is not your fault some drunk asshole ran a red light.
那也不是你的错
Then it's not your fault, either.
我想妈妈看到我们共度
I think Mom would be happy we're
生命中的最后时刻  会很开心的
spending our last few minutes together.
这不是我们的最后时刻
These are not our last few minutes.
等等  奎茵
Wait, Quinn.
相信我
Trust me.
奎茵  你要干什么  奎茵
Quinn! What are you gonna do? Quinn!
不  我刚做完一台手术
No, I just finished a procedure.
每天拯救一次生命
Saving lives one day at a time.
好吧  宝贝  你回去工作吧
Okay, honey, I'll let you get back to work.
我也爱你  再见
I love you, too. Bye.
你不该来这里
You shouldn't be in here.
我想感谢你救助我妹妹
I wanted to thank you for helping my sister.
还有
And...
来向你道歉
say that I'm sorry.
为什么
For what?
所有事
For everything.
我一直在想那天事情会怎么发展
I can't stop thinking about how things could've gone that day.
我理解你行事的动机
I understand why you did what you did.
是我置你于那样的情形下
I put you in that position.
要是我那时
If only I had followed through with
遵从了自己的内心就好了
how I really felt in that moment.
我只是害怕了
I was just scared.
狗屁
Bullshit.
你觉得我傻吗
You think I'm stupid? Hmm?
你到底想怎么样
What do you really want?
我想要回我的工作
I want my job back.
你说过我们都乐于助人
You said that we both like helping people.
所以说不定你能帮我
So maybe you can help me
而且我
and I...
也能帮你
...could help you.
好了  你在干什么
Okay, what are you doing?
你在录音吗
You recording this?
你想的话可以搜我身
Search me if you want.
我在侧室等你
I'll be in the closed wing.
来吧
You should come.
不来也行  决定权在你
Or don't. It's up to you.
禁区
奎茵
Quinn?
来找我吧
Come find me.
说老实话
You know, I'm not gonna lie,
我没料到有这一出
I didn't see this one coming.
你掉东西了
You dropped something.
闭上眼睛说  "马克"
Close your eyes and say, "Marco."
我喜欢
I like this.
马克
Marco.
波罗
Polo.
马克
Marco.
波罗
Polo.
马克
Marco.
波罗
Polo.
我听见你的呼吸声了
I can hear you breathing.
贱人
Bitch!
-那他妈是什么  -吗啡
- What the hell is that? - Morphine,
足够让你死三回了  人渣
enough to kill you three times, you piece of shit!
奎茵  不要
Quinn, don't!
不是他就是你
It's either him or you.
你看见了吗  它救了他
Did you see that? It saved him.
会有用的
This is gonna work.
什么会有用
What's gonna work?
他有那个软件
He has the app.
如果他在指定时间前死去  就会打破诅咒
If he dies before he's supposed to, it'll break the curse!
奎茵
Quinn!
奎茵  你在哪
Quinn, where are you?
疯女人  那他妈是什么鬼
Crazy bitch! What the hell was that thing?
无所谓了  我会告诉警察
Doesn't matter. I'll tell the cops
你是怎么把我引诱到这里来
how you lured me back here.
我又是怎么出于正当防卫不得不杀了你
How I had to kill you out of self-defense.
你的时间到了  你这个强奸犯人渣
Your time's up, you rapey fuck!
什么鬼
Shit.
乔丹  乔丹
Jordan. Jordan!
乔丹
Jordan.
我不想死  我不想死
I don't wanna die. I don't wanna die.
离她远点
Get away from her.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
我爱你  乔丹
I love you, Jordan.
我会一直在你身边
I'll always be with you.
奎茵  不要
Quinn, don't!
奎茵小熊
Quinny Bear.
妈妈
Mom?
你那天晚上去哪了
Where were you that night?
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
我在找你
I was looking for you.
我知道
I know.
我想你
I miss you.
我也想你  宝贝
I miss you too, baby.
过来
Come here.
不
No.
你没法再控制我们了
You're not in control anymore.
而我会
I am.
奎茵  不要
Quinn, no!
奎茵
Quinn!
不
No!
来人救救我
Somebody help me!
奎茵
Quinn!
求你了
Please.
求求你别离开我
Please don't leave me.
求你了
Please.
求求你别离开我
Please don't leave me.
求你了
Please.
纳洛酮[吗啡受体拮抗剂]
快点  快点  快点
Come on, come on, come on.
一定要有用
Please work.
快点  快点  快点
Come on, come on, come on.
一定要有用  拜托了
Please work, please.
奎茵  醒醒
Quinn, come on.
你看
See?
我说过我会一直在你身边
I told you I'd always be with you.
我爱你
I love you.
生日快乐  妈妈
Happy birthday, Mom.
挚爱的母亲
Jamie Harris
真漂亮
They're beautiful.
天哪
Oh, my gosh.
又有三个女人指认了沙利文医生
Three more women came forward about Dr. Sullivan.
他应该要蹲很久监狱了
Looks like he's going away for a long time.
很好  他罪有应得
Good. Serves him right.
我只是庆幸没人会受到伤害了
I'm just glad no one else is gonna get hurt.
回家吗  奎茵
Coming to the house, Quinny?
我得先去趟医院
I have to stop at the hospital first.
-你要和我一起去吗  -好
- You wanna come with me? - Yeah.
-好吧  我在家等你们  -好
- All right. I'll see you guys at home. - Cool.
走吗
You coming?
软件更新
倒忌时2.0已安装
怎么了
What's wrong?
-再来点吧  -不了  谢谢  不用
- A little more? - No, thank you. No.
我们喝光了
Oh. We killed it.
我得告诉你一件事
I gotta tell you something.
既然我们了解对方一些了
Now that we know each other a little bit,
我想说你比资料照片上丰满多了
you are a lot chestier than your profile pic.
谢谢夸奖
Oh. Thanks.
你和照片完全不像
And you don't look anything like yours.
-多谢夸奖  谢谢  -一点也不像
- Appreciate that. Thank you. - At all.
好了  我第三次修改了你们的账单
Okay. I revised your check for the third time.
而且我们半小时前就打烊了  所以
Also, we closed a half hour ago. So...
我们很喜欢这里
We love it here.
我想也是
I'm sure you do.
-真不错  -是啊
- What a catch. - Yeah.
我不清楚你的数据套餐
I don't know what your data plan is,
但我可以给你弄到八五折  说不定八折优惠
but I can get you a 15, maybe 20% discount.
我去一下洗手间
I'm gonna use the ladies' room.
好的  我就在这等你  亲爱的
Okay. I will be here, my darling.
好
Yeah.
什么鬼
What the hell?
有人吗
Hello?
我们还在这呢  拜托  老兄
Dude, we're still here. Come on, man.
老兄
Dude.
什么鬼
What the hell?